<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Internone</string>
    <string name="ift">"(1) People get exposure to new culture.

(2) People who work in this new atmosphere seek more than
just employement out of their work. This accounts for a lot
of development in not just technical terms but in social terms too.

(3) People get a different and new experiance which is very beneficial when they return back to india.

(4) An FT in itself does nothing to improve one's CV greatly."</string>
    <string name="htb">(1) The basic thing is that you should
have an awareness about your interests regardless of your stream/department.
Past projects that you did during your vacations can help you finding your area
of interest and also will help during foreign training.\n\n\n
(2) You’ll then want to look closely at the courses offered by the institutions on
your shortlist, as well as researching
the local area and lifestyle, admission requirements and costs.\n\n\n
(3) Once you’ve firmly decided on your
 program and institution, you should
  start to think about your application(s).
   Application processes differ depending on the university and the country, but generally each institution will provide full details of how to submit your application on the official website.\n</string>
    <string name="wtb">:- Considering your application as early as possible is the best way to go.
        After all, the sooner you gain acceptance into a university,
        the sooner you can arrange your travels. To avoid disappointment,
        note down all the relevant application deadlines (set out by your chosen university) in HUGE LETTERS on your calendar.\n\n
    :- Application deadlines will be different depending on the school, but, for programs starting in the fall (September/October),
        applications will generally be open from early in the year (January/February) until the middle of the year (June/July).\n</string>
    <string name="cgpa">:- Eligibility criteria for different streams and different foreign universities are different.
    In general, a good CGPA (above 8.0) will work.\n\n
    Does it imply that students with CGPA less than 8 can not avail a foreign internship?\n
    Well, surely not the ones which have explict cut-offs listed. But, you do opportunities at par with them.\n
    !!The only Eligibility criteria is your passion and your primary motive!!</string>
    <string name="wir">You may be asked to provide some supporting documentation as part of your application.
        Once again, requirements vary depending on the country and university, but international students are often asked to provide the following:\n\n

:- Passport photos for identification\n
:- A statement of purpose\n
:- CV/résumé\n
:- Academic references/ letters of recommendation\n
:- Certificate and transcripts of your secondary education\n
:- Proof of English-language proficiency (e.g. a TOEFL/IELTS certificate, for schools in English-speaking countries), or other language test\n
:- Admissions test results (e.g. GMAT/GRE results, for graduate programs)\n</string>
    <string name="ap">There are few clear steps that stand out to get a foreign internship, with exponentially decreasing order of importance.\n\n

1. Get a really good CGPA (8.5+)\n
2. Identify professors in your academic field (was Physics for me)\n
3. Write really good SOPs (do some research)\n
4. Upload your CV (some filter out unknown emails with attachments)\n
5. Send out emails on Tuesday (inboxes get cleared on Mondays)\n</string>
</resources>
